Mss.B.St65p
American Philosophical Society
- Series I. Correspondence
  - Johnson, Charles F., 1939
  - Johnson, Clifford S., 1952
  - Johnson, Eric Warner, 1952-1972
  - Johnson, Mrs. Henry Alden, 1968
  - Johnson, Julian, 1952
  - Johnson, Lois, 1951
  - Johnson, Lyndon B., 1960
  - Johnson, Marjory, 1965
  - Johnson, Nancy Riddle, 1941-1943
  - Johnson, Paul B., 1952
  - Johnson, Walter, 1965
  - Johnson & Johnson, 1946-1948
    A clinical study of a lotion containing hexachlorophene...
  - Johnston, Charles G., 1946
  - Johnston, David T., 1953
  - Johnston, Joseph A., 1944-1967
  - Johnston, Marion Northup, 1952-1965
  - Johnston, W.W.S., 1954-1955
  - Johnstone, E.R., 1941
  - Johnstone, Mr. and Mrs. Edward L., 1966-1967
  - Jolly, Hugh, 1952
  - Jones, Albert M., 1939-1962
  - Jones, Annette R., 1944
    Elizabeth B. Garrison
  - Jones, C. Clothier, 1966
  - Jones, Chester M., 1939-1968
  - Jones, Dorothy Bovee, 1943
  - Jones, Edward B., 1967
  - Jones, Fred L., 1955-1956
  - Jones, Helen E., 1943
  - Jones, J. Albright, 1944-1958
  - Jones, James E., 1961
  - Jones, Nancy, 1948
  - Jones, R. Frederick, 1946
  - Jones, Ralph, 1955, 1960
  - Jones, Robert Cuba, 1951-1952
  - Jones, Robert K., 1955
  - Jones, Robert R., 1960
  - Jones, T. Duckett, 1941-1942
  - Jonxis, J.H.P., 1952-1957
  - Jonxis, Willy, Undated
  - Jordon, Edward H., 1961
  - Jordan, Frances, 1958-1961
  - Jordan, W.K., 1953
  - Journal for Medical Sciences, 1949
  - Journal of Chronic Disease, 1954
  - Journal of Clinical Investigation, 1946
  - Journal of Pediatrics, 1952-1961
  - Journal of Social Medicine, 1947
  - Joy, Frederick B., 1953
  - Judelsohn, Louis, 1942
  - Julliard, Jean, 1960
  - Justi, Charles M., 1950
  - K and H Distributors, 1950
  - Kabat, Elvin A., 1961-1968
  - Kadish, Arnold H., 1962
  - Kagan, Benjamin M., 1965-1966
  - Kahhan, Sheldon, 1948
  - Kahl, Eugen, 1948
  - Kahn, Walter D., 1947-1950
  - Kaighn, Charles B., 1946
  - Kaiser, Edna Lou, 1942-1943
  - Kalkstein, Mrs. Elizabeth, 1967-1969
  - Kaminester, Sanford, 1961
  - Kampmeier, R.H., 1962
  - Kandle, Roscoe P., 1949,1966
  - Kane, Arthur R., 1966-1968
  - Kane, Lewis W., 1948
  - Kanel, Lilly, 1950
  - Kaplan, Bruce, 1964
  - Kaplan, Eliot Frederic, 1961
  - Kaplan, Martin M., 1960, 1964
  - Kapur, O.P., 1953
  - Kardon, Mr. and Mrs. Robert, 1958
  - Karel, Leonard, 1956
  - Karelitz, Samuel, 1959
  - Kark, Robert M., 1951
  - Karlberg, Peter, 1964
  - Karp, Robert J., 1967
  - Karpoof, Alex D., 1961
  - Karr, Walter G., 1940, 1943
  - Karreman, George, 1961
  - Karrer, H.E., 1950
  - Karush, Fred, 1952-1969; 3.0 folders
  - Katcher, Avrum Labe, 1953-1959
  - Kato, Katsuji, 1949, 1954
  - Katz, Geneva, 1962
  - Katz, Helen, 1956
  - Katz, Martin, 1962
  - Katz, Ricardo, 1950-1956
  - Katz, Samuel L., 1962
  - Katzka, Irwin, 1956
  - Kauffman, M. Luther, 1949
  - Kaufman, Jeffrey L., 1967
  - Kay, William R., 1968
  - Kaye, Robert, 1945-1971; 3.0 folders
  - Kean, B.H., 1959
  - Keaney, George, 1948
  - Keefer, Chester S., 1944-1954
  - Keegan, A.P., 1942
  - Keidan, S.E., 1956
  - Keilman, Grace, 1948
  - Keiser, E. Lee, 1959
  - Keitel, Hans, 1956-1972
  - Keiter, W. Eugene, 1953
  - Keller, Charles, 1950
  - Keller, William F., 1964, 1968
  - Kelly, Claire E., 1944
  - Kelly, Francis, 1961
  - Kelly, Frank B., Jr., 1949
  - Kelly, James R., 1970
  - Kelly, Le Moyne Copeland, 1960
  - Kelly, Nora, 1948
  - Kelly, Patrick J., 1963-1965
  - Kelly, Richard S., 1952
  - Kelly, William D., 1964
  - Kelner, Jan, 1958-1962
  - Kelsey, Lynne G., 1958
  - Kelsey, Weston M., 1960
  - Kempe, C. Henry, 1953-1966
  - Kempf, Sofie, 1941-1942
  - Kendall, Edward H., 1940
  - Kendall, Norman, 1941-1954
  - Kendig, R.C., 1966
  - Kennedy, Charles, 1950-1967; 3.0 folders
  - Kennedy, H.E., 1968
  - Kennedy, Hughes, Jr., 1951
  - Kennedy, Mr. and Mrs. Melville T., 1966
  - Kennedy, V. James, 1958
  - Kennedy, William B., 1953-1965
  - Kenney, A.S., 1953
  - Kent, Kathleen, 1959
  - Keogh, William, Undated
  - Kerelitz, Samuel, 1948
  - Kerman, Willard Z., 1957
  - Kern, C. William, 1940, 1961-1962
  - Kern, Richard A., 1939-1952
  - Kerpel-Fronius, E., 1947
  - Kerr, Charles M., 1946
  - Kerr, George T., 1944
  - Kerrigan, Gerald A., 1969
  - Kety, Josephine and Seymour, 1948-1959
  - Keuper, Deborah, 1962
  - Khalil, Ahmed Fouad, 1960
  - Khan, A.M., 1946
  - Kidd, Dr., 1946
  - Kiel, Frank W., 1953
  - Kiesewetter, William, 1950-1959
  - Killingsworth, W. Price, 1941-1961
  - KIm, Bong Taik, 1961
  - Kim, Hi-Soo, 1959
  - Kim, Ih Chin, 1958-1959
  - Kimball, Fiske, 1945
  - Kimber, John H., 1944-1945
  - Kimber, W.M.C., 1944
  - Kimble Glass Company, 1945
  - Kimbrough, Robert A., 1945, 1962
  - Kimmel, Robert, 1961
  - King, Allen, 1959
  - King, Garfield, 1965-1966
  - King, John T., 1951
  - King, Orville C., 1941-1942
  - King, Richard B., 1949
  - King, Trudy, 1968
  - Kinsell, Laurence W., 1949-1954
  - Kinsey, Alfred C., 1944
  - Kiossoglou, Kosmas A., 1960-1965
  - Kirber, Herbert P., 1946, 1956
    Also used the surname Kirchenberger.
  - Kirk, Kathleen E., 1945
  - Kirk, Marion S., 1958
  - Kirk, Marjorie Jane, 1950
  - Kirn, George J., 1956
  - Kirschner, Richard, 1962
  - Kirsh, David, 1953
  - Kirsopp, Edgar C.B., 1959
  - Kislova, L.D., 1958
  - Kissick, William L., 1968-1970
  - Kitay, William, 1959
  - Kitts, Albert Warren, 1949-1966
  - Kjellberg, Knut, 1952
  - Klarman, Herbert E., 1962
  - Klatskin, Gerald, 1951, 1959
  - Klauder, Mrs. Louis T., 1950
  - Kleckner, Martin, 1959
  - Klein, Charles David, 1942
  - Klein, Dorothy Ellen, 1962
  - Klein, Mrs. Jerry, 1956
  - Klein, Joseph M., 1946-1950
  - Klein, Robert, 1950
  - Kleinerman, Alida L. Carey, 1965
  - Kleinhenn, Raymond, 1955
  - Klemperer, Paul, 1955
  - Klenner, Fred R., 1962
  - Kline, Joseph J., 1951-1961
  - Kline, Judith, 1958-1959
  - Kline, Oram, 1944-1945
  - Klingensmith, Linda, 1961
  - Klous, D. Donald, 1947
  - Kneeland, Yale Jr., 1946, 1961
  - Knight, Albert P., 1939-1968
  - Knight, Clinton Prescott, Jr., 1961
  - Knight, Vernon, 1953-1966
  - Knisely, Kristine, 1952, 1965-1970
  - Knobloch, Howard T., 1940-1945
  - M. Knoedler and Company, 1959
  - Knott, Angela, 1967
  - Knott, Elizabeth M., 1948-1950
  - Knotts, Glenn R., 1965
  - Knox, James E., 1950
  - Knudsen, Robert T.A., 1946
  - Knutti, Ralph E., 1959-1961
  - Ko, Kook Hoon, 1955
  - Koblenzer, Peter J., 1959-1968
  - Koch, Karen, 1954, 1960-1961
  - Kochenderfer, Thomas T., 1946, 1956
  - Koenig, Lester, 1956
  - Kolbe, Henry W., 1965
  - Koleski, John, 1961
  - Koller, Mrs. W.S., 1955, 1968
  - Kolmer, John A., 1946
  - Kometani, John T., 1957
  - Komrower, George, 1947-1963
  - Konowich, Paul Alan, 1961
  - Konzelmann, Frank W., 1950-1951
  - Koonce, Donald B., 1950
  - Koop, C. Everett, 1946-1970
  - Koprowski, Hilary, 1956-1964; 2.0 folders
  - Korsin, Barry, 1962
  - Kotzen, Herman F., 1940-1962
  - Kouri, Pedro, 1941-1942
  - Kover, Joseph, 1971
  - Koweity, Shafik, 1946
  - Koyama, Takeo, 1968
  - Kozloff, Henry, 1949, 1951
  - Kozlov, Harold, 1951-1961
  - Kraft, Ruth M., 1942
  - Krainin, Philip, 1953
  - Krakow, Mr. and Mrs. Simon, 1956
  - Kralik, John J., 1948
  - Kramer, Benjamin, 1959
  - Kramer, J.B., 1964
  - Krasnoff, Howard, 1969-1970
  - Krasnogorski, Dr. and Mrs., 1961, 1965
  - Kravis, Lillian P., 1946, 1951
  - Krayer, Otto, 1948
  - Kreidberg, Marshall B., 1953
  - Kreitz, Paul Brooks, 1949-1950
  - Kretchmer, Norman, 1961
  - Krevsky, Seymour, 1961
  - Kritzler, Robert A., 1961
  - Krogman, Wilton Marion, 1931-1971; 3.0 folders
  - Kroonenberg, J., 1951
  - Kroungold, Margie, 1961
  - Krouse, Theodore B., 1947
  - Krowitz, Joseph, 1946
  - Krueger, Albert P., 1941-1942
  - Krugman, Saul, 1964-1971
  - Krumbhaar, E.B., 1933-1955
  - Kuder, Katherine, 1946
  - Kudo, Shinsaku, 1963
  - Kugelmass, I. Newton, 1961
  - Kuhn, Daisy, 1952, 1966
  - Kuhn, Richard, 1950-1967
  - Kuhns, William J., 1959
  - Kumagai, Mitio, 1956, 1960
  - Kumm, Henry W., 1959
  - Kung, Cora Lee, 1966
  - Kunin, Esther, 1943
  - Kunkel, A.H., 1947
  - Kunz, Lea, 1966-1967
  - Kuo, Peter T., 1965
  - Kurtz, Charles H., 1948-1952
  - Kurtz, Margaret Taylor, 1955
  - Kurtz, Sanford Robert, 1964
  - Kuttner, Ann G., 1941
  - Kwashiorker, 1954
  - Kyle, George Clayton, 1964
  - Kylstra, J.A., 1957
  - Kyman, Seymour, 1946
  - LaBoccetta, A.C., 1948-1969
  - Lace, Richard E., 1946
  - Lachman, Joseph, 1955
  - Ladd, William E., 1945
  - Lade, James H., 1960
  - Ladimer, Irving, 1961
  - Lafond, Mrs. Edward T., 1948
  - Lagercrantz, Rutger, 1958
  - Lahdensuu, Sakari M., 1952
  - Laidlaw, P.P., 1938
  - LaMar, Norvelle Chappell, 1964
  - Lamb, Carolyn, 1967
  - Lamb, Robert L., 1967
  - Lambertsen, Dr., 1955
  - Lamp, Albert L., 1967
  - Lampe, Kenneth, 1965
  - Lamy, Maurice, 1947-1957
  - Lancet, 1953
  - Landis, Eugene M., 1947
  - Landis, Mrs., 1967
  - Landsberger, E.K. Georg, 1954-1960
  - Lane, Harold M., 1956
  - Lang, David J., 1959
  - Langbaum, Elliot, 1963
  - Langbaum, Sybil, 1954
  - Langdon, David E., 1959
  - Langley, L.L., 1966
  - Langmuir, Alexander D., 1952-1959
  - Langworthy, Mr. and Mrs. David, 1967
  - Lapan, Bernard, 1953
  - Largey, Arthur M., 1958
  - Larimer, R.N., 1962, 1967
  - Larkin, Edward P., 1961
  - Larkin, Florence, 1966-1970
  - Larkin, Michael, 1963-1964
  - Larkin, Roosevelt and Larkin, 1946
  - Larsen, Jean W., 1960
  - Larson, Burneice, 1952-1953
  - LaSalle, Roberta, 1957-1964
  - Lash, Dorothy, 1947
  - Latham, Elizabeth B., 1957
  - Lathbury, Vincent T., 1953
  - Lathrop, Fred, Jr., 1956
  - Lathrop, Frederic W., 1950-1953
  - Latner, A.L., 1959
  - Lattomus, W.W., 1951
  - Lauer, A.R., 1965, 1969
  - Laufer, Maurice W., 1958
  - Laurance, B.M., 1961
  - LaVan, Donald, 1958
  - Lawrence, Edward, 1961
  - Lawrence, John S., 1948
  - Lawrence, Kingsley, 1967
  - Lawrence, Pearl, 1965
  - Lawrenceville School, 1946-1948
  - Laws, Elizabeth, 1969
  - Lawson, David, 1964
  - Lawson, George S., 1947
  - Lawson, Robert B., 1954-1965
  - Lax, Henry, 1953
  - Layton, William C., 1962-1963
  - Lazer, Joan, 1961
  - Lea & Febiger, 1947
  - Leader, George M., 1954
  - Leal, Alberto B., 1953-1954
  - Leaman, William G., Jr., 1946, 1954
  - Lear, Walter J., 1971-1972
  - Leavell, Byrd S., 1948
  - Leavering, Mrs., 1965
  - LeBouvier, George, 1956
  - Lechaux, Pierre Aymar, 1950-1954
  - Lecks, Harold, 1954-1959
  - Lee, Daniel, 1961
  - Lee, Henry F., 1946-1971; 2.0 folders
  - Lee, Jean Gordon, 1969-1970
  - Lee, Philip R., 1964, 1966
  - Leebron, J.D., 1948-1950
  - Leeuwen, G. Van, 1970-1971
  - LeFamine, Armand A., 1962
  - Leffingwell, Sanford, 1963
  - Lefkoe, Harold, 1952
  - Lefton, Cebe, 1966-1968
  - Leggio, Jerome P., 1967
  - Lehman, Charles A., 1948, 1964
  - Lehn and Fink Products Corporation, 1953
  - Lehnen, Mr. and Mrs. J., 1958
  - Lehr, Herndon B., 1965
  - Leidy, Philip L., 1951
  - Leinbach, Harvey, 1952
  - Leiter, Laban W., 1951
  - Lejeune, Jerome, 1960
  - Lemaitre, George D., 1958
  - Lenher, Samuel, 1963
  - Lennette, Edwin H., 1947
  - Leo, Thomas, 1950
  - Leonard, John C., 1949, 1958-1959
  - Leonard, Martha F., 1951
  - Leopold, Irvine, 1955
  - Leopold, Simon S., 1952-1953
  - Lepore, Michael J., 1970
  - Lepper, Mark H., 1960
  - Leslie, Warren D., 1958
  - Lester, John A., Jr., 1963, 1966
  - Letwin, Lawrence E., 1954
  - Levan, Albert, 1960
  - Levan, Johan Albert, 1960-1961
  - Lever Brothers Company, 1956
  - Levi, Florence Dalsimer, 1963, 1967
  - Levine, Samuel Z., 1935-1962
  - Levinson, Kim, 1961
  - Levis, Mercedes Louise, 1961-1962
  - Levy, Isaac D., 1945-1954
  - Levy, Leona O., 1966
  - Levy, Michael H., 1945
  - Lewey, F.H., 1948
  - Lewis, E. Gaynor, 1948
  - Lewis, Karsten C., 1970
  - Lewis, Margaret, 1951
  - Lewis, Marvin A., 1952
  - Lewis, Robert M., 1947
  - Lewis, Robert V., 1952
  - Lewis, Shippen, 1946
  - Liang, Esther Chang, 1947-1957
  - Liberty Mutual Insurance Company, 1946
  - Librenjak, Kate, 1960-1961
  - Lichtinger, Kuba, 1947
  - Lichty, Dr., 1937
  - Lieber, Holly, 1961
  - Lieberman, David J., 1967
  - Lieberman, John, 1956-1961
  - Liebman, Marvin, 1960
  - Lief, Florence Suskind, 1955-1968
  - Life Magazine, 1955-1956
  - Lightner, Elmer, 1963
  - Lightwood, Reginald, 1956, 1971-1972
  - Likoff, William, 1947
  - Lilienthal, Joseph, 1955
  - Lilly, John C., 1966
  - Lin, Feng-Kai, 1955
  - Lincoln, Isabel R., 1951
  - Lind, John, 1953-1955
  - Lind, Paul, 1961
  - Lindahl, Ann M., 1971
  - Lindau, Warren, 1962
  - Lindsay, D.C., 1945
  - Lindsey, Walter H., 1950
  - Linton, Mrs., 1946
  - Linton, M. Albert, 1960-1966
  - Lippincott, Gregory, 1961-1964
  - Lippincott, Horace Mather, 1953-1954
  - J.B. Lippincott Company, 1948-1960
  - Lippman, N.L., 1946
  - Lipschutz, Arthur, 1946
  - Lipscomb, Laura L., 1948-1949
  - Litchfield, Harry R., 1946, 1950
  - Little, Brown & Company, 1953
  - Littlefield, John W., 1952-1953
  - Littlejohn, Clarence G., 1955-1961
  - Liu, Charlotte, 1957
  - Liu, Oscar C., 1948-1959
  - Liu, Pin Pin, 1947
  - Livingood, Clarence C., 1947-1948
  - Livingston, Robert B., 1966
  - Livingston, Samuel, 1955, 1970
  - Lizzeralde, Eduardo A., 1959
  - Lober, Lillias, 1945
  - Locke, LeRoy D., 1946
  - Lockwood, John S., 1943
  - Loda, Frank, Jr., 1961
  - Loeb, Robert F., 1968
  - Loeffler, John G., 1954-1963
  - Logan, George B., 1958
  - Logan, J.S., 1946-1950
  - Logan, John V.R., 1960
  - London, Arthur Hill, 1955-1957
  - London, Carol Caine, 1965
  - Long, C.N.H., 1963
  - Long, Diana Michele, 1961
  - Long, Julius T., 1960
  - Long, Perrin H., 1950-1965
  - Longcope, Warfield T., 1946
  - Longmaid, Sydney E., 1952
  - Longpre, Daniel, 1947
  - Longshore, William Allen, 1952
  - Longstreth, Thatcher, 1970-1971
  - Loomis, Norman R., 1964
  - Loomis, Valerie, 1961
  - Loosli, Clayton G., 1947
  - Lord, Mary P., 1951
  - Lord, Robert M., 1950-1955
  - Lore, Harry Elmer, Jr., 1947-1948
  - Lorram, Alvina, 1946
  - Lotspeich, William, 1968
  - Louis-Charles, Roy, 1962
  - Lovejoy, Elizabeth, 1952
  - Lowe, Charles U., 1953, 1965-1968
  - Lowenburg, Harry, 1948-1960
  - Lowenthal, Martin, 1951
  - Lowry, Grace, 1943-1946
  - Lowry, W. Norwood, 1961
  - Lucas, Mary Suzie, 1954
  - Lucchesi, Pascal F., 1946-1947
  - Lucke, Baldwin, 1948
  - Ludington, Nicholas S., 1954-1955
  - Ludwig, Ernest H., 1952
  - Luecke, Percy, 1948
  - Lukens, Frances, 1958
  - Lukens, Francis D.W., 1963
  - Lukens, Lewis N., 1954
  - Lull, George F., 1950
  - Lundahl, Anne B., 1945
  - Lundstrom, Rolf, 1956-1970
  - Lunt, Beverly, 1946
  - Lupu, Harvey Gerald, 1961
  - Lurie, David, 1954
  - Lurie, Max B., 1959
  - Lyman, Margaret, 1964
  - Lynch, Delia A., 1951
  - Lynch, John F., Jr., 1947-1949
  - Lynch, Theresa I., 1949
  - Lynn, Mrs. C.E., 1956
  - Lyon, George M., 1940
  - Lyon, George P., 1947, 1966
  - Lyon, Julian M., 1945-1951
  - Lyons, Edwin L., 1961
  - Lyons, Robert, 1948
  - Lyttle, John D., 1947-1948
  - Mabey, Marjorie, 1942-1944
  - MacBride, Katharine Elizabeth, 1960
  - MacCall, Alexander, 1967
  - MacCallum, Fred O., 1948-1959
  - MacCarroll, D. Randall, 1943
  - MacColl, Alexander M., 1970
  - MacColl, W.A., 1965
  - MacDonald, Colin, 1940
  - MacDonald, Kenneth, 1940
  - MacDonald, Sharon, 1948
  - MacGuire, Hugh C., 1955
  - Machella, Thomas E., 1952, 1960
  - Machlan, Iris Ann, 1949
  - Macht, Stanley H., 1952
  - MacIntosh, Archibald, 1941-1954
  - MacIntosh, Charles A., 1959
  - Mack, J. Keller, 1949
  - Mack, Pauline Beery, 1941-1953
  - MacKenzie, G.M., 1947
  - MacKenzie, Robert A., 1946
  - MacKinney, Loren C., 1951, 1957
  - Mackintosh, Helen K., 1960
  - Mackler, Bruce, 1956-1957
  - Maclary, Mrs. Robert, 1957
  - MacLean, Mr. and Mrs. Paul D., 1941-1971
  - MacLeod, Colin M., 1946-1970
  - MacLeod, Paul F., 1957
  - MacMillan Company, 1965
  - MacNamara, Jean, 1932
  - MacNeal, Perry S., 1962
  - MacNish, John, 1940
  - Macrae, A.D., 1955
  - Madeira, Mr.and Mrs. Percy C., 1940-1950
  - Madow, Leo, 1966
  - Madsen, Sten, 1953-1971
  - Magath, T.B., 1952
  - Maggio, C.I., 1954
  - Maghen, Khalil, 1962
  - Magill, James P., 1959
  - Magness, Mark, 1961
  - Mahon, Ina, 1950
  - Maico, Stethetron, 1947
  - Makinsky, Alexander, 1942
  - Malcolm, W.G., 1940
  - Malen, Maurice, 1943-1950
  - Mallinckrodt Chemical Company, 1953
  - Mallory, Roberta F., 1964
  - Malloy, 1953
  - Maloney, James V., 1971
  - Mancini, Stephen, 1961
  - Mancrieff, Alan, 1947-1948
  - Mandell, Joseph L., 1949-1950
  - Manganella, Michael P., 1951
  - Manger, Donald F., 1961-1962
  - Mangold, Francoise, 1949-1955
  - Mangold, Dr. amd Mrs. Renward, 1953
  - Manissadjian, Antranik, 1961
  - Manley, Derrill B., 1959
  - Manno, Peter J., 1955-1968
  - Manrodt, Kurt, 1943
  - Mantell, Harriet Baylies, 1951-1956
  - Mara, 1946
  - Marceau, Mr. and Mrs. Henri, 1968-1969
  - Marcy, Harry K., 1952
  - Marden, Phillip A., 1950, 1967
  - Margileth, Andrew, 1953
  - Margolin, Joseph B., 1960
  - Margolis, Bernard, 1967
  - Margolis, Frederick J., 1948, 1961
  - Margolis, Julius, 1966
  - Marin, Juan Bosch, 1950-1951
  - Marin, Ramiro Arcia, 1944
  - Marino, Jean M., Undated
  - Maris, Elizabeth, 1942-1955
  - Mark, Mrs. Helen Wheeler, 1954, 1961
  - Marka, Myer, 1947
  - Marks, Meyer B., 1949
  - Marquis, Henrietta L., 1945-1969
  - Marsh, Frank H., 1955
  - Marston, Robert Q., 1971
  - Martin, Alexander T., 1951
  - Martin, B.B., 1951
  - Martin, Donald S., 1961
  - Martin, Edward, 1953
  - Martin, Jon Charles, 1961
  - Martin, Nicholas H., 1950
  - Martin, Peter, 1967
  - Martin, Samuel, 1970
  - Martwick, Mrs. Lawrence, 1968
  - Mascio, Frank, Jr., 1961
  - Mason, Alfred B., 1955
  - Mason, Ernest C., 1959
  - Mason, James O., 1960
  - Masse, Nathalie P., 1954, 1962
  - Massie, Maud Wilson, 1955
  - Massons, Jose M., 1952-1953
  - Mastroianni, Luigi, Jr., 1969-1970
  - Matecki, F.M., 1969
  - Matthews, LeRoy W., 1959
  - Matthews, Richard, 1950
  - Matumoto, Minoru, 1952
  - Matusan, Cynthia, 1961
  - Mauger, Isabel S., 1946
  - Maul, Cynthia, 1962
  - Maule, E., 1946
  - Maurer, Paul H., 1957-1960
  - Mauro, Joseph, 1942
  - Maxfield, William, 1964
  - Maxwell, Doris B., 1966
  - Maxwell, John F., 1938-1939
  - May, Charles D., 1951-1961
  - May, Hans, 1948
  - Maycock, W. d'A., 1948-1951
  - Mayer, Andre, 1945
  - Mayer, Florence E., 1955
  - Mayflower Hotel, 1940
  - Mayo, Charles W., 1959-1960
  - Mayo, Leonard W., 1952
  - Mayock, Robert L., 1961
  - Maysent, H.W., 1969
  - Maza, Carlos, 1952
  - Mazo, Milton, 1948
  - McAllister, Jean C., 1940-1966
  - McAllister, Robert M., 1959-1971; 2.0 folders
  - McBride, William K., 1944
  - McBryde, Angus, 1950-1959
  - McCabe, Edward S., 1958
  - McCabe, James L., 1968
  - McCance, R.A., 1952-1958
  - McCandless, Esther L., 1956-1957
  - McCarthy, Eugene, 1968
  - McCarthy, James F., 1965
  - McCarthy, John, 1962
  - McCarthy, Thomas, 1964
  - McCartney, J.L., 1941
  - McCarty, Arthur C., 1943
  - McCarty, Ethel, 1944
  - McCaslin, Lee, 1965-1966
  - McClelland, Charles Q., 1958
  - McClelland, David C., 1963, 1966
  - McClelland, Laurella, 1961
  - McClenahan, Mr. and Mrs. John L., 1957, 1968
  - McClenahan, William J., 1954
  - McClenahan, William U., 1940-1968
  - McClendon, S.J., 1957-1958
  - McClure, Norman E., 1945
  - McCluskey, Edmund R., 1940-1954
  - McClusky, Thorp, 1949
  - McCollester, Duncan L., 1960-1961
  - McCollum, E.V., 1941
  - McCollum, Robert W., 1961
  - McComb, James A., 1961
  - McConnell, James W., 1939
  - McConnell, Jeannette, 1947
  - McCorkle, Sara, 1947
  - McCoy, George W., 1941
  - McCoy, J., 1958-1959
  - McCracken, J.C., 1940
  - McCracken, J.P., 1949
  - McCreary, J.F., 1956-1958
  - McCroan, J.E., 1960
  - McCrory, Wallace W., 1946-1968
  - McCue, Howard and Carolyn, 1947
  - McCulloch, Hugh, 1965-1970
  - McDaniel, Walter Brooks, 1940, 1958
  - McDonald, Francis G., 1940
  - McDonald, Joseph J., 1957, 1960
  - McDougall, Clarice, 1946-1948
  - McElhenney, Thomas J., 1950
  - McElhenney, Thomas R., 1952
  - McFadden, William M., 1971
  - McFarlan, A.M., 1946
  - McGavran, Jean, 1954-1955
  - McGee, Elizabeth L., 1954
  - McGee, Maureen, 1961
  - McGee, W. Ambrose, 1947, 1950
  - McGeorge, Mary, Undated
  - McGinley, Siobhan, 1960-1963
  - McGowan, John, 1942
  - McGrath, Edward F., 1940-1947
  - McGraw-Hill Book Company, 1952-1966
  - McGuinness, Aims C., 1941-1968; 4.0 folders
  - McGuire, Paul J., 1949
  - McGuire, William F., 1954
  - McIlvain, Mrs. William E., 1952
  - McIntosh, Gertrude, 1945
  - McIntosh, Rustin, 1940-1966; 2.0 folders
  - McKay, Mrs. R.B., 1947
  - McKay, R.J., 1952-1966
  - McKay, Mr. and Mrs. Russell, 1967
  - McKelvy, William Graham, 1963
  - McKenna, Ernest L., 1967
  - McKeown, John, 1969
  - McKhann, Charles F., 1939-1954
  - McKibben, John Mead, 1943
  - McKinley, C. Scott, 1940
  - McKinley, E.V., 1969
  - McKinley, Robert C., 1965, 1970
  - McKusick, Marjorie Jane, 1962
  - McKusick, Victor A., 1966-1967
  - McLane, Bayard, 1950
  - McLaughlin, Bruce, 1961
  - McLaughlin, Henry, 1962
  - McLean, C.C., 1955
  - McLean, Dr. and Mrs. David, 1959-1962
  - McLean, Harry, 1939
  - McLean, John D., 1939
  - McLean, Ross L., 1957-1960
  - McLean, William, Jr., 1933
  - McLendon, Preston A., 1953-1959
  - McLorinan, H., 1951
  - McMenemey, Ruby, 1949
  - McMillan, Thomas III, 1965
  - McMorrow, Kathryn J., 1945-1947
  - McNally, Donald J., 1964
  - McNamee, William B., 1970
  - McNee, Sir John, 1952-1953
  - McNiel, J.R., 1962
  - McNinch, J.H., 1949
  - McPadden, Arthur J., Jr., 1957-1960
  - McPhedran, Alexander, 1949-1956
  - McPhedran, Mr. and Mrs. F. Maurice, 1941-1952, 1971
  - McPhedran, Peter, 1965-1969
  - McQuarrie, Irvine, 1943-1961
  - McSparren, Clark, Jr., 1964
  - McVey, Mrs. J.F., 1954-1955
  - Meade, Gordon M., 1943
  - Meade, Mrs. Richard, Jr., 1940
  - Meade, Stanley, 1954-1955
  - Meader, Fred M., 1941
  - Means, J.H., 1942
  - Measey, William Maul, 1961
  - Meconochie, Mrs. H.D., 1941
  - Medal of Freedom, 1946
  - Medical Administration Service, Inc., 1938-1945
  - Medical aid to Cuba, 1962
  - Medical alumni, 1969
    Saint Joseph's College
  - Medical care, Undated
  - Medical economics, 1957
  - Medical letter, 1965
  - Medical news, 1957-1967
  - Medical Press, Inc., 1952
  - Medical Radio System, 1959
  - Medical Record and Annals, 1955
  - Medical science, 1957-1958
  - Medical Tribune, Inc., 1965
  - Medical World News, 1969
  - Medicare and Medicaid, 1971
  - Medoff, Harold S., 1945-1951
  - Medovy, Harry, 1958
  - Mee, Edward, 1962
  - Meglino, Theresa, 1961
  - Meigs, Johnny, 1949
  - Melbin, Mrs. J., 1959
  - Mellbin, Tore, 1957
  - Mellinkoff, Sherman M., 1955
  - Mellish, R.W. Paul, 1961-1963
  - Mellman, William J., 1954, 1960
  - Mellor, A.B., 1945
  - Melnick, Joseph L., 1951
  - Melton, Frank M., 1961
  - Melville, Dorothy E., 1946-1961
  - Melville, Harry, 1963
  - Melvin, Frank L., 1968
  - Memorials, 1972
  - Meneghello, Julio, 1942
  - Mengert, Ulrich J., 1941
  - Mengert, William F., 1943
  - Mennen Company, 1955-1956
  - Menninger, Karl, 1965
  - Mensching, Fritz, 1949-1954
  - Merchant, Donald J., 1971
  - Merck and Company, 1942-1965
  - Merck, Sharp and Dohme, 1957
  - Meredith, John M., 1962
  - Mereu, Tullio, 1959
  - Merkle, V.J., 1961
  - Merrick, John Vaughan, 1956
  - Merrill, M.H., 1951
  - Merritt, Mrs. Elizabeth, 1961-1963
  - Messinger, Paul, 1960-1962
  - Metropolitan Life Insurance Company, 1944-1950
  - Metzger, I.D., 1943
  - Meyer, Bernard C., 1953
  - Meyer, Dorothy A., 1939
  - Meyer, Harry M., Jr., 1969-1970
  - Meyer, K.F., 1942
  - Meyerhof, Otto, 1941-1952
  - Michie, Alexander J.
  - Middelkamp, J. Neal, 1957
  - Mid-Town Motor Inn, 1969
  - Mileris, V.J., 1964
  - Miles, J.A.R., 1950
  - Miles, Ward C., 1960
  - Millar, Hilary Ethel Clara, 1952-1953
  - Miller, C. Arden, 1966
  - Miller, C. Phillip, 1954
  - Miller, D.P., 1964
  - Miller, Duon H., 1952
  - Miller, Elmer H., 1940